RESUME AND CURRICULUM VITAE





PROFILE

- # MOHAMMAD REZZA DANIAL BIN MD AMIR
- # 23
- # 14 MAY 1995
- # KLANG VALLEY / PENANG

CONTACT

NO4, LORONG 15 /SS2 BANDAR TASEK MUTIARA 14120, SIMPANG AMPAT, PULAU PINANG.

+6017 482 5310 rezzadanialcs@gmail.com www.rezzadanial.com

AREAS OF EXPERTISE & SKILLS

- Web Design
- HTML, CSS, jQuery
 - Angular.js
- Graphic Design
- Data Center
- Penetration Testing
- Cloud Computing
- iOS Development

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2018 Intern at Novatis Resources Sdn Bhd

- Six months on-site experience in Data Center
 Maintenance
- Handle servers installation and migration
- Develop web application using Angular.js

2017 - Trainer under Malaysia Digital Economy
Present Coorperation (MDEC)

Consult and train a local citizen about government digital economy programs. Helps

EDUCATION

2018 Universiti Teknologi MARA (Shah Alam)

2015 Universiti Teknologi MARA (Perlis)

2012 SM Sains Tun Syed Sheh Shahabudin (Penang)

SOFTWARE

Bootstrap

Adobe Creative Suite

VMware vCenter

Digital Ocean



PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: MOHAMMAD REZZA DANIAL BIN MD AMIR

Age: 23

Date of Birth: 14 MAY 1995

Home Address: NO4, LORONG 15 /SS2 BANDAR TASEK

MUTIARA, 14120 SIMPANG AMPAT,

PULAU PINANG.

Reside: Klang Valley

Mobile: 017 482 5310

Email: rezzadanialcs@gmail.com

Website: https://www.rezzadanial.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rezza-danial-568113139

Notice Period: 9 July 2018

PROFILE

I am **all rounded** young professional intending to continue my development as a **iOS Developer**. I think in term of results and objectives, I am **workaholic**, and I work with decisiveness and full with **passion**. I have a **proactive attitude** and find positive ways to stimulate and engage with any group of community. Even though I just 23 years old, I have a lot of **professional experience** in many field. I was trained to be a great leader with strong physical and mental readiness. In term of social life, I am a friendly person and able to cope with every kind of social group.



EDUCATION

MAC 2016 – JULY 2018	Bachelor Degree in Netcentric Computing		
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	 MARA Technology University, Shah Alam Major in Web Development and Computer Networking Relevant Courses: CCNA, Web Technologies and Networking Final Year Project: Unifying Crowdsourcing Platform using Ruby on Rails Current CGPA: 3.21 		
JUN 2013 – NOVEMBER 2015	Diploma in Computer Science		
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	 MARA Technology University, Perlis Learnt general and fundamentals of all computer science branches Relevant Courses: Object Oriented Programming, Multimedia, Data Communication, Operating System CGPA: 3.06 		
2011 – 2012	Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)		
THE STORY OF THE S	 Sekolah Menengah Sains Tun Syed Sheh Shahabudin Science and ICT stream SPM: 5A, 3B, 2C 		

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

FEBRUARY 2018 – JULY 2018	Intern at Novatis Resources Sdn. Bhd.	
novatis (resources	 CDB Perdana 2, Persiaran Flora Cyber 12, Cyberjaya Assist Engineer during Data Center maintenance. Learn about Servers Virtualization, Networks Equipment, Storage and Backups and Tape. Familiar with servers from IBM, HP, DELL, and Lenovo. Provide technical drawing for client's documentation. Web Development using Angular.Js 	
MAY 2016 – PRESENT	Trainer under Malaysia Digital Economy Cooperation (MDEC)	
Driving Transformation	 Consult and train a local citizen about government digital economy programme. Facilitate them to earn side income from doing online jobs. Conduct a presentation at organizations about Digital Economy. 	
JULY 2015	Production Operators at Western Digital	
Western Digital®	 Western Digital (Media), Bayan Lepas, Penang Six months experience cumulative in manufacturing industrial as production operator. manufacturing computer hard disk storage. 	
JUNE 2014 – OCTOBER 2015	Instructor Assistant	

MARA Technology University, Perlis



- Assist the Instructor during Co-Curriculum activities such as rope climbing, abseiling, marching, first aid course.
- Plan and manage co-curriculum course for approximately 2000 students each semester.
- Manage the student's files and attendance.

TECHNICAL CERTIFICATIONS



CyberSecurity Fundamentals Exam (CSX)

- License number: 2017-1098939-CSXF
- Covered all fundamental aspect of Cyber Security in an Organization.
- Risk Assessment
- Network Security



Certified IP Associate (CIPA)

- License number: CIPA.1503422
- Covered deep Internet Protocol course.
- IP Configuration and Design
- Network Monitoring

TECHNICAL COURSE



Server Infrastructure Penetration Testing

- Hands on training in Penetration Testing
- Learn Ethical Hacking
- Port Scanning
- Linux Security/Hacking Tools

All certificates can be view in my LinkedIn Profile.

HONOUR AND ACHIEVEMENT

	Young Lieutenant (Kesatria)
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	Commissioned as Young Officer for Kesatria uniform body.
الدوائية فالمالة المحافظ	DEAN AWARD
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	Awarded for Excellent Result in Academic
WELTERBE	MOUNT KINABALU EXPEDITION
A IONOW AND A STRING	Has successfully climbed Mount Kinabalu summit at 13,435 feet from sea level.

All certificates can be view in my LinkedIn Profile.

LANGUAGES

•	Bahasa Malaysia	English
	 Written: Excellent 	

o **Spoken:** Excellent

o Reading: Excellent

Written: Excellent

o **Spoken:** Excellent

o **Reading:** Excellent

MAJOR SKILLS

SKILL	PROFECIENCY	DESCRIPTIONS
Web Design	Intermediate	Good in Front-End Development
		HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular.js
		UI/UX design
Graphic Design	Expert	Experienced in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator
		Online or Offline Content
		Logo and Icons design
iOS App	Beginner	Familiar with Swift programming
Development		Experienced in Xcode IDE
		Setting Layout for multiple screen size devices
Web	Intermediate	Experienced in development using Ruby on
Development		Rails.
		Good understanding in MVC
IT Operation	Intermediate	Good knowledge in many Linux distros
		Data Center Infrastructure
		Servers and Network Installation and
		Configuration.
		Penetration Testing

Kindly visit **www.rezzadanial.com** for more details about my skills.

REFERENCES

1) Anas Repin

• Relation: Senior System Engineer at Novatis Resources Sdn. Bhd.

• Contact: 018 3799660 / anas@novatis.com.my

2) Dr. Shahniza Binti Kamal Bashah

• Relation: Lecturer at UiTM Shah Alam

• Contact: 019 212 2622 / shahniza@tmsk.uitm.edu.my

3) Hj. Khalidah Binti Abdul Karim

• Relation: Previous Employer

• Chairman of Pusat eRezeki Shah Alam

• Former Chief Financial Officer at Bank Negara Malaysia

• Contact: 012 218 6655